Excuse me, sir. Sir, question
for you. Have you ever been...
Oh my God.
I've seen your shit.
Yeah? Could I interview you real quick?
Okay, I'm totally rich. Relax.
Is this your Rolls Royce?
Yes.
And what do you do for
a living out here in Miami?
I own Poppy Steak.
Best restaurant in the world.
What's the biggest issue you've had so far in terms
of revenue? What's the most you've made in a year?
2021. Over $100 million.
In business, I've done over $2 billion.
$2 billion.
But what if you have a bad month in business?
I could never figure that out, and I haven't had a bad month ever
since I put Juul cigarettes on the market and started doing $150 million a year.
How can somebody become a
multimillionaire like yourself in today's world?
Listen.
Hard Knocks family, it is 6.30 in the morning, and we are about to fly from
Austin, Texas to Miami, Florida to go interview some of the wealthiest people in the entire city.
Miami has 75% more millionaires now
than it did a decade ago.
So we're going to go find the hidden wealth in
Miami and go figure out where these multimillionaires and billionaires are.
So that way we can figure out how they got to where they were
and how you can start your path to becoming financially free in today's world.
So with that being said, let's head out
to Miami and get this video on the way.
All right, you guys, we just touched down in Miami, Florida, and we are at our first
stop in the design district, home to some of the most expensive luxury stores in the city.
So we're going to walk around, find some wealthy people,
figure out how they created their wealth in the city.
We're going to walk around.
Looks like we got one right here.
So come on, let's see.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
Have you ever been broke before?
Real quick.
No, I haven't.
All right, my friend.
All right.
Hey, as you guys can see, since we're in Miami in the design district, like I said, this
is home to some of the most successful people in the entire country, our base here in Miami.
So all we can do is kind of keep tracking until we find these yeses and
get some real game and real business advice from how these people created their wealth out here.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you, sir.
Have you ever been?
No, thanks.
No.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
No, I know you.
I know you.
I'm not going to.
I'll do it.
No, no, no, no, no.
You are not doing it.
It's going to go on TikTok.
Real quick.
I'll do it.
No, no, honey.
We cannot afford to do things like this.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
Have you ever been broke before?
I know this one.
Real quick.
I started a channel in Austin.
I know.
I've seen it.
You've seen it.
Have you been broke before?
Have you ever been broke before?
What's your name?
James.
What are you guys?
I started a channel.
I grew it to 7 million followers in Austin, Texas.
Okay.
I'm totally rich.
Relax.
Real quick question for you.
What line of business were you in?
Money laundering.
Actually, though.
I don't want to get into it.
Okay, one question.
Yes.
That's it.
In 60 seconds, somebody wants to become financially
free in today's world, give them the blueprint.
What does it take to become successful
like yourself in the business world today?
Psychology.
Understand human nature.
And don't push people.
But when it comes to sales, though,
how do you leverage psychology in sales?
How do you leverage psychology in sales?
I'm just really fucking smart.
Are you old money or new money?
I did it myself.
Could I walk with you?
Huh?
Could I walk with you real quick?
In your opinion, what was the hardest skill
for you to master in the business world?
Waking up.
What do you mean by that?
I don't like to wake up in the morning.
In terms of delegation, how important was
it for you learning how to master delegation,
building teams, and bringing the right people in?
It's impossible.
I do everything myself.
What was the best financial advice
you ever got from a mentor?
Take the money.
Don't keep putting it back in.
Why is that?
Because you keep spending your money.
But what if you have a bad month in business?
I could never figure that out, and I haven't
had a bad month ever since I put Juul cigarettes
on the market and started doing $150 million a year.
You do $150 million a year?
$170 million.
I work with Tyson, Future, everybody.
How did you scale from an
eight to a nine figure company?
That's incredible.
When opportunity meets preparation, you have luck.
What was your risk tolerance as a business owner?
I just go for it.
Yeah?
Did you have to borrow money from
banks or leverage any capital from investors?
How did you get the money?
I did it myself.
Now I borrow money from banks.
They're begging to give me money.
At 8%, they'll do anything to give me money.
What's your name, sir?
Johnny.
I appreciate you.
What do I see this on?
The School of Hard Knocks, all platforms.
We do 120 million views a month.
Real quick, one more for you, real quick.
How old are you now?
With everything you've learned, one message
to the younger generation today that could
help them start that path and that learning curve?
I can't.
I just had to go through what
I had to go through to get here.
I had to just do it.
I had to do it,
make mistakes, do it, make mistakes.
But I learned, and I'm smart.
Were you close to bankruptcy at any point in time?
Twice.
How'd you break that and overcome that?
I started over again, a
chunk of a car at 40.
Incredible.
Thank you for your time, sir.
You're welcome.
All right, you guys.
That's got to be one of the
wildest interactions I've ever had running this channel.
That's that $150 million entrepreneur we just
caught out here in Miami, Florida, and he
just gave us some straight game for you guys.
Crazy interview to get this video rolling.
We got to keep it rolling.
Go get this next one.
Come on, you guys.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, question for you.
Have you ever been broke before?
No.
No?
Bro, I started the channel in Austin.
I grew up to 7 million followers.
I interview business owners all over the country.
Can I get just one
minute of your time real quick?
Please?
It'll be worth it.
I promise you.
Question for you.
Oh, I know you.
Could I interview you real quick?
Real quick.
One minute.
I'm about to walk into a meeting.
Please.
I've got a huge fan of yours.
It'll be worth it.
Trust me.
One minute.
Awesome, man.
Thank you, bro.
I appreciate that.
All right, you guys.
So yesterday was not easy, man.
We got the one interview, but like I
said, man, these are super high net worth individuals.
We just tried to get that one right there.
He likes the channel, but what is he doing?
He's going into a meeting on a Saturday right now.
We just got to keep up the pressure
and go find where these multimillionaires and billionaires
are out here in Miami, Florida.
So come with me.
We're going to tag these interviews.
Come on.
Is this your Rolls Royce?
Yes.
And what do you do for
a living out here in Miami?
I own Poppy Steak.
So you own a restaurant.
How long have you been- Best restaurant in the world.
Haven't you heard of Poppy Steak?
How long have you been in the restaurant business for?
About five years.
Five years.
Yeah.
And what's the biggest you've had
so far in terms of revenue?
What's the most you've made in a year?
We made a lot during the COVID years.
Florida's been good to us.
Yeah.
And then thank God, business is booming.
Give me your range.
We just keep going up
and up and up and up.
What's the biggest year you had at your restaurant?
What'd you do in revenue?
We don't like to say numbers, but a lot.
A lot of money.
Yeah.
Enough.
Enough to get this car.
Yeah.
You can see for yourself.
Just keep driving, bro.
Keep driving.
So how did you scale to
multiple locations and overall just the business?
You got to always give the
best service, best hospitality, the best team.
You got to have the best team behind you.
You got to put a lot of love
into it and a lot of hard work.
Yeah.
Now when it comes to networking, a
lot of people struggle to build relationships, build
connections in the business world.
You're in the hospitality, you're in the people business.
What does it take to build
winning relationships in the business world?
You got to constantly stay honest, be honest
with all your friends, be honest with all
your investors and just keep
printing money and make success.
So how did you get
the money to start this business?
Did you have to borrow capital from banks
or investors or how did you ultimately get
the money?
It's always like that.
You know, in business you need friends,
you need relationships, you need partners, but
you got to stay true and loyal to your partner.
And have you ever been broke before?
Of course.
What the fuck does that mean?
So you don't-
I'm self-made.
I worked very hard to get to where I am.
So what was the turning point?
Many times.
So what was the turning point to financial freedom?
Like, what did you see that made you
want to stand out and go create a multimillion
dollar business?
It's never, never ending.
There's never financial freedom.
You always got to work harder and you
always got to thrive to get more and more.
And your last message to somebody
trying to become a multimillionaire in today's
world?
You got to stay true to your brand
and believe in yourself and work very hard.
Do you believe in God?
Of course.
And how important was faith for you?
Very important.
All these things are very important.
Thank you, my friend.
Have a great day.
Have a great day, sir.
Thank you.
Hey, yo, we just interviewed, I think his
name is David, but he's the owner of Poppy
Steak.
One of the largest steak houses in the area.
He's the owner of the entire country.
We just held up traffic for, I
don't know, at least three to five minutes.
Never sleep on Miami, you guys.
Great interview.
Let's keep the video rolling, man.
Shout out Miami.
Let's go.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, question for you.
Have you ever been...
Oh my God.
I've seen your shit.
Yeah?
That's crazy.
Could I interview you real quick?
I don't know.
I don't know if I want to answer your questions.
Yeah?
What made you pick me out?
Man, you just had to look.
You just, you looked like you got money, bro.
This is crazy.
Are you filming this shit?
Yeah.
This is crazy.
Are you filming this shit?
Yeah.
This guy at my gym comes up to
me, David Genicello, yesterday and says to me, you've
got to watch this guy.
And I said, I watch him all the time.
Wow.
But I never thought I'd get interviewed.
That's insane.
Yeah.
Well, I guess like what
line of business are you in?
I set up gyms around the world.
I sell gym equipment around the world.
So you have a, you're an entrepreneur.
I'm an entrepreneur.
How long have you been a business owner for?
18 years.
And over these 18 years, what's
the greatest lesson you've learned about entrepreneurship
you pass off to someone about to
start their first company in today's world?
Believe in yourself.
Always.
How did you find that self-belief
to go make millions of dollars?
It's one of the biggest things.
People struggle with.
I think I had this burning desire inside of
me from a young boy, but every time I was
told no, I continued to push through.
And the more people that talk shit about me,
the more that made me even like, like it gets
me emotional even thinking about it because I
was one of them that like, you count me
out.
I'm going to do it point blank period.
And so I just kept going and going and going.
And I never in a million years
thought I'd be where I'm at today.
So you don't come from a lot of money.
No, no.
My dad's, uh, um, comes from
Athens, Greece, uh, immigrant come from nothing.
And then raised me to be who I am today.
But you never took no for an answer.
Did like when I say never took no, like
15 years ago, me and her were robbing Peter to
pay Paul like eating peanut butter and jelly sandwiches.
I'm trying to be on Mr. Olympia stage
bodybuilder and fucking like, you know, kept going, literally
taking cash to pay the electric bill.
And then, you know, kept grinding.
I used to run 400 ads literally
a week on Craigslist to sell my equipment.
Nobody knew who I was.
And then 2015 hit a hundred thousand followers
on Facebook and then just kept grinding, bro.
Yeah.
So out of 10 businesses, they
won't make it past five years.
From your perspective, what's the most common
mistake you see business owners make in today's
world?
So it's funny in the gym world, about three,
three out of 10 is going to make it.
And so what I normally see them do
is they fail before they even get open.
Meaning they've got half a
million dollars to open this gym.
They want to go come to me
and spend three, four or 500,000 on equipment.
I say, Whoa, they went into the
high dollar district like we're at right now.
And they say their rent's
$38,000 a month for a gym.
They have no money in the bank to back them.
They're setting themselves up for
failure from the very get go.
Before they even open.
So I always tell them, I sit down with
them and I say, okay, what budget are we working
with?
What is your rent?
What is your paywall?
Are you going to put into hours or are you
trying to pawn it off and pay somebody a hundred
grand a year?
If you're not willing to put in the work,
it is no businesses that get rich quick point
blank period.
So I always tell people, I'm like, if you
want to put into work, you can make it, but
you got to be able
to fucking sleep at the business.
I appreciate you, my friend.
You got amazing advice.
Pleasure.
Arch, you guys, Miami has been insane so far.
We're back out here for day three.
Headed to go get our next interview.
But I want to take a quick moment to
talk to you about one of the greatest things I've
learned running this channel.
45% of millionaires in the United States
have a side hustle where they're making additional
money.
That's why I want to talk about
the sponsor of today's video prize picks.
Whether you're working a nine to five or
running your own business, prize picks gives you the
ability to make some extra money
while you're already on the grind.
If you're like me and have a passion
for sports and play fantasy football every single year,
you might as well learn how
to turn that passion into profit.
That's why with prize picks.
All you need to do.
Is pick two or more football players every
week and pick more or less on their projected
stats.
Then you just have to place your entry.
You're already spending the time
watching and studying football for fantasy.
So you may as well transfer some
of that knowledge to make some extra money.
And if you can make the right decisions, you
have the ability to turn $10 into a thousand
with just a few taps from your phone.
So to join me and sign up for prize picks
today, all you need to do is go to prizepicks.com
slash S O H K and use code
S O H K for a guaranteed $50.
That's it.
Once you play $5 in lineups, once again, go
to prizepicks.com slash S O H K use code S
O H K for a guaranteed $50.
Once you play $5 in lineups with all that
being said, go tap in with prize picks right
now, but let's go ahead to
our next destination out here in Miami.
Come on.
I've got a very special surprise for you guys.
We're about to interview Anthony Powell.
He's done over $2 billion in sales throughout his career.
We're linking up with him at the Porsche
design tower where he just got a new penthouse.
This is one of the top five.
With these buildings in the world, there's
over 20 billionaires that live here and he's
about to drop some serious game for you guys.
So with that being said, let's go link up
with Anthony and see what he has to say.
Anthony, what's going on my friend?
Hey buddy, how you doing?
Good to see you.
Good to see you as well.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
I started in direct sales
and contact management and lead distribution.
Are you a business owner?
Yes, I am.
How long have you been an entrepreneur for?
25 years.
Throughout your career, what has been the
most amount of money that you've ever made
in a single year?
In business, I've done over $2 billion.
$2 billion.
What's your secret to selling in a competitive industry?
Well, everyone knows McDonald's.
Why is McDonald's successful?
Because they have a systematic approach to their business.
And number two, the system's so good that
a 15 year old can run the business.
I created that with digital products.
I have a system that's so
watertight with contact management, lead distribution, and
LMS, no matter what product or
service I put in, I just win.
It's the system.
You have to have a
system if you want to win.
They're a formula.
Yeah, you got to have a system.
I'm a master system creator.
And I know.
I just launched another business.
Guess what?
We launched it back in November.
Boom.
It's like this.
Why?
The system.
What is the best financial decision
somebody can make in today's world?
Number one, find a vehicle that make lots of money.
That's called earned income.
Number two, don't spend your earned income.
Invest it in assets.
But everyone goes, okay, I've heard this 100 times.
What do I do?
Where do I put my first 10 grand, 20 grand?
What do I do to compound cash?
You got to get an S&P ETF.
The S&P has outproduced everything over the years.
For example, this year, it's already up 17%.
That means if you had
100 grand, you're already up 17,000.
You put 500, 1,000, 250, whatever you can
afford every single month, you put it into
an S&P ETF and let it grow and work
your ass off in your vehicle and your business.
Number three, once you get to a certain
point and you have money compounding, start investing
in multifamily.
You know, one thing I did when I
was broke, I needed my rent paid for.
So I went and bought an 8-plex.
The bank will lend you because
you're not, it's not a personal residence.
They want to see cash flow.
Does those eight residential units pay the debt load?
Yeah.
The answer is yes.
So therefore, those seven people paid the debt load.
I got it for free.
I was able to increase the
value, sell it, and double the money.
And when your passive residual income kicks off
what you want as far as your goals and
dreams, now you can start spending your money
on Lambos and houses and Porsche Towers and
all the fun stuff.
I don't spend earned income.
Whether I work or not, sitting here with
this guy, I'm making money right now standing here.
That's what you got to be doing.
All right, you guys, my guy Anthony just dropped
a billion dollars worth of game for you guys.
But I've got another special surprise for you.
We were about to go interview
Miami legend Eric Spofford on his yacht.
For those of you who don't know,
Eric sold a company for over $100 million.
And he wants to drop $100
million worth of game for you guys.
So we're going to head there right now.
Come with us.
Let's go see what Eric has to say.
Yo, yo, what's going on, my friend?
What's going on, man?
How you doing?
Man, this is fire.
This is crazy, man.
Sweet.
Let's go.
Who am I here with today?
Eric Spofford, baby.
Throughout your career, what has been
the most exciting thing for you?
What's been the most exciting thing for you?
Who am I here with today?
Eric Spofford, baby.
Throughout your career, what has been the
most amount of money that you've ever made
in a single year?
2021, over $100 million.
$100 million.
Yeah.
And what happened that year
that you made over $100 million?
I sold my business for $115 million
on December 21st, four days before Christmas 2021.
That's a crazy Christmas present.
It was.
And what was your business?
It was the largest provider of
addiction treatment services in New England.
And why was that your vehicle?
Like that's a niche business.
Out of any business you could have been
in, how did you end up in that business?
I got sober and into recovery.
I beat myself, man.
I beat a drug habit, beat alcoholism at
21 years old and found a passion for helping
other people, turned it into a
business, blew it out of the water.
Where are we at right now?
Miami, Florida, Island Gardens Marina, standing in
front of my boat, the bonus rounds.
This is your yacht?
That's my yacht.
As a nine figure entrepreneur, what is
the best financial decision that somebody can
make in today's world?
Get into Section 8 real estate right now.
The reason I say Section 8 real estate
is that people live with the delusion that they
need hundreds of thousands of dollars and
a lot of expertise to become successful.
You always want to own an Alumeta zero SEA.
If you're not as affluent as me and
you have a sense of sanctity or serviceability you
don't want to get into muy queers.
That includes the illی doing a lot of
money with opportunities and living in the suburbs
but the fact that maybe you finally startedingo
up a den and that means that's where you
are now is a real asset class.
Everybody wants to become a real estate investor.
The beautiful thing about this asset class
is our average price per property is under
$100,000 and almost any ordinary average American
can get into becoming a real estate
investor in this asset class.
And it also produces higher than average
cash on cash returns because the federal government
overpays on the rent to incentivize
landlords to create more low-income housing, because
there is a shortage of national crisis.
What's the difference you'd say?
crisis of not enough low-income housing for people
that are at or below the poverty line.
And so if you're watching this and
you're like, I'm just an ordinary, average American,
working middle-class type person, get out of
the financial slave mindset. And instead of taking
your earned income and spending it directly
on your lifestyle, reduce your lifestyle a little
bit, save your money, take your savings
and put that savings into an appreciating cash-flowing
asset that is going to pay you every month
to earn it. And if you do that consistently enough,
there'll become a breaking point where you have
enough money coming from your real estate assets
to pay for your lifestyle. And at that
exact moment is when you will become financially free.
The amount of stress you endure every day will
go down substantially. And you get to do this very,
very cool thing, which happened for me a long
time ago as a result of investing in real estate.
I do things because I want to, not because
I have to. Most of you do things because you
have to. You know they don't teach
that in school, right? They certainly do not.
Your last message to the younger generation,
give them the blueprint. Give them a 60-second
business masterclass right now. How can somebody
become a multimillionaire like yourself in today's
world? What does it take? Listen, there's a
couple core principles before I get to the
business masterclass that the young generation really
needs to embrace and embody. Because if
you miss this, you'll miss all of it. Drugs
and alcohol are for losers. If you do drugs and
alcohol, the chances of you ever being financially free...
Drugs and alcohol are for losers. If you miss this,
you'll miss all of it. Drugs and alcohol are for losers.
are immensely financially successful are almost zero. You want to
be successful, you want to live a life like this,
drugs and alcohol are not involved. Here's another
important thing for you. Your circle matters more
than you realize. I see too many young
people hanging out, being cool, hanging out with losers,
doing loser stuff. If you want to be a winner,
you have to look around the people around you and be
honest with yourself. Are these my friends, my
boys, people I love? Or are they actual winners?
Why are you hanging out with them?
You must have somewhat of a cold-hearted, ruthless nature
to you and have your loyalty be to your
future in how you surround yourself with your
people. I'm not telling you to tell those people
to get out of here and never talk to them again
and break up with them and all that. Love them from
a distance, but chase relationships with winners
and successful people that are like-minded, that
want the same things. If you do those two things,
stay away from vices and hang out with people that
are destined to be successful, it is almost guaranteed to be successful. If you do those two things, stay away
from vices and hang out with people that are destined to be successful, it is almost guaranteed to be successful.
If you do those two things, stay away from vices and hang out with people that
are destined to be successful, it is almost guaranteed that you will find a level of success.
Thank you so much for
your time, sir. I appreciate that.
So my guy, Eric, just came through again
with the crazy interview at the yacht. But guys,
that's a wrap on today's video. Be sure to
like and subscribe for amazing content we've got coming
very, very soon. And as I mentioned earlier
in the video, our official entrepreneur community gives
you guys the ability to join and get
access to the multimillionaire and billionaires that I interview
on this channel, where you can learn skills directly from
them, like how to sell, how to market, how to
build businesses, how to create wealth in different
industries. You can talk to them directly on the
live calls that I'm hosting every single week
and get access to tons of exclusive content.
So to join, click the link down in the description
below. I can't wait to see on the inside of the
School of Mentors. But with that being
said, we'll see you in the next video.